让我们简要地分析一下这种方法。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Let's
briefly analyze this approach.
在结对编程之后我们会看到,
And we'll see this now
after pair programming,
这是一种比较新的方法。
it's sort of a newer
approach to this model.
方法的问题。
Problems of the approach.
很多时候，这些背景功能，功能
A lot of the time,
these background features, the function
然后自动调用，后台特性获取一些数据。
that's then automatically called,
the background feature gets some data.
例如，如果背景功能是通过网络传播的,
So for example, if the background
feature's speaking over the network,
得到一些新的数据，那么，这些数据会出现在哪里呢？
to get some new data in, well then,
where's that data gonna show up?
这些数据显示为输入,
That data shows up as the input,
自动插入到运行的 printHello 函数。
automatically inserted into the running
of that printHello function.
真是太神奇了。
That's pretty amazing.
但问题是，这意味着数据只是可用的
But the problem with that is that
means that data is only available
在 printHello 函数的执行上下文中。
inside the execution context
of that printHello function.
所以如果你去了 Twitter，抓取了一些数据，这个函数会
So if you've gone off to Twitter, grabbed
a bunch of data, the function that's gonna
自动运行完成这个是在 Twitter 的后台,
run automatically own the completion of
this being to Twitter in the background,
这个函数会自动运行。
the function's gonna run automatically.
它会输入来自 Twitter 的数据。
It's gonna have its input
be that data from Twitter.
你只能在函数中使用这些数据,
You could only use that
data inside that function,
因为我们不能运行这个函数。
because we don't get to run this function.
因此，我们不能让它返回任何东西。
Therefore we can't have
it return anything out.
因为我们不能在任何地方分配它的返回值。
Because we can't assign
the return value of it anywhere.
所以取而代之的是，所有的数据都将在这里面使用。
So instead, that data's all
gonna be used inside of here.
这是相当粗糙的。
That's pretty rough.
这就是所谓的回调地狱,
And that's what created something
known as callback hell,
我们所有的工作都是在一个功能中完成的。
where we are doing all of our work on that
data from Twitter, inside of one function.
正如我们在函数内部，在函数内部所做的功能。
As we do function, inside a function,
inside a function.
我看得出来，这很粗糙。
That's pretty rough, I see that.
但是我要告诉你们的是，我们实际上在做什么
But I'm gonna show you that,
in terms of what we're actually doing
在后来的新版本中，引擎盖下面，变化不大。
later on in a newer version,
under the hood, it's not changing much.
但是在可读性方面，它使它更好。
But in terms of readability,
it makes it much better.
我甚至不知道我是否完全同意这一点。
I don't even know if I
fully agree with this.
也许把一个功能分解成另一个功能有点奇怪
Maybe it feels a little odd to think of
parting a function into another function
只是让它运行得更晚。
only for it to run much later.
看，我们经过 printHello。
Look, we pass in printHello.
只是让它在很久以后自动运行。
Only for it to run automatically,
much later.
但是只要你生活在一种语言中，你就会使用背景知识
But as long as you live in a language
where you're going to use background
语言之外的特征，你不可避免地会这么做，对吗？
features outside of the language,
you're kinda inevitably doing that, right?
你不能，没有真正的解决办法。
You can't, there's no real way around it.
你要依靠背景知识,
You're gonna rely on that background,
这个网页浏览器本身就带有 JavaScript，可以把这个函数带回浏览器中
the web browser itself with JavaScript
to bring that function back in for
你和运行它，当它知道后台工作已经完成。
you and run it when it knows
the background work is done.
好处，我会说这种风格，超级明确，超级点击。
Benefits, I'll say of this style,
super explicit, super click.
一旦你知道它实际上是如何工作的，它就变得相当简单，相当公平。
Once you know how it's actually working,
it's fairly kind of simple, fairly.
你等着看下一个版本吧。
[LAUGH] Well,
you wait till you see the next version.
至少在这里，它相当直接。
At least here, it's fairly direct.
我接受一个函数，我把它附加到背景功能,
I take in a function,
I attach it to the background feature,
当后台特性完成后，它会被放入队列中。
it gets put in the queue when
the background feature is done.
即使这是一个0毫秒的特性，它也会出现在背景中。
Even if it's a 0 millisecond feature,
it goes in the background.
说清楚点 Brayden 这就是为什么即使它是个0毫秒计时器,
Yeah, to be clear, Brayden, this is why
even though it's a 0 millisecond timer,
只要它被去掉了 printHello 函数,
as long as it's being thrown
out the printHello function,
要排队才能进去。
it's gotta queue up before
it's allowed back in.
我认为，这种方法的另一个问题是
The other, I think,
problem with this approach is that for
错误处理，不是很干净。
error handling, it's not as clean.
你等待直到你看到承诺的方法。
You wait til you see the promise approach.
它的错误处理非常好。
Its error handling is super nice.
我们将看到，人们，虽然，在一些结对编程。
We will see that, people, though,
after some pair programming.
你会看到一个快速拨号 / 异步，你知道如何运行，并得到结对编程。
Gonna see a speed dial/async, you know
how to pan out, and get pair programming.